welcome to the ICICI Prudential family
congratulations on purchasing ICICI brew
I protect smart this is an introductory
video guide to your policy after going
through this short video you will have a
clear understanding of the benefits
which this plan offers and the things
you need to do to ensure that you get
these benefits let us first start off
with the free look period to ensure that
you are comfortable with this product we
provide you with a 15-day period from
the time you receive the policy document
to understand the policy if you find
that there are aspects of the policy
that you are not comfortable with you
can return the policy to us and you will
be eligible for a refund let us now
start with the guided tour of your
policy when applying for your ICICI Prue
I protect smart policy you would have
made three important choices the number
of years for which you want the
insurance benefit of ICICI Prue I
protect smart the amount of insurance
that you want to cover yourself for and
whether you would want the insurance
benefit to be paid to your family as a
lump sum or spread over time these three
factors determine your policy benefits
so we request you to go through your
policy kit to ensure that your policy
correctly reflects the choice you made
when applying for it to get these
benefits you only have to do one thing
pay your premiums regularly year after
year
do make a note of your next premium duty
and pay your premium to ensure
continuous life insurance protection for
you and your loved ones now let us
understand the benefits of ICICI brew
I protect smart ICICI Prue I protect
smart is a life insurance policy with a
single objective of providing life
insurance cover to the policyholder in
the unfortunate event of the death of
the person covered by this policy the
life insurance amount will be paid to
the nominee specified by you while
purchasing your policy there are three
ways in which the life insurance amount
can be paid to the nominee option 1 the
nominee gets the entire insurance amount
at one time option 2 the nominee
receives the insurance money as a
monthly income over 10 years option 3
the nominee receives monthly income for
10 years with a 10% increase every year
please refer to your policy document to
understand which option you have
selected apart from this there are two
other features of your ICICI Prue I
protect smart policy which you should
make note of first if the person covered
by this policy has an accident and
suffers a permanent disability the
future premiums of ICICI Prue I protect
smart will be waived off and the
benefits of the policy will continue
second in a situation where the person
governed by this policy is detected with
the terminal illness the life insurance
amount will be paid to the nominee to
summarize the three core features of
ICICI Prue I protect smart our life
insurance amount will be paid out to the
nominee in the unfortunate event of the
death of the person covered by this
policy in case of permanent disability
due to an accident future premiums will
be waived off and the benefits of the
policy will continue in case the person
covered by this policy is detected with
a terminal illness the insurance amount
will be bailed apart from these score
benefits of ICICI Prue I protect smart
there are two optional benefits which
will apply to policyholders who have
opted for these additional benefits
critical illness cover today we see and
hear about lifestyle related diseases
becoming increasingly common it is
important that we be prepared for such
situations under this feature if the
person covered in this policy gets
diagnosed with any of the 34 major
illnesses covered in this plan
ICICI Prue I protect smart will pay the
critical illness cover amount to take
care of hospital expenses medical care
expenses and possible loss of income
arising from these diseases the critical
illness cover amount will be specified
in your policy document accidental death
cover
this is yet another optional benefit of
ICICI brew I protect smart in case you
have opted for this feature the next
section of the video will be of interest
to you in case the person covered by
this policy dies due to an accident the
amount paid to the nominee will be two
times of the life insurance amount do
note that both critical illness cover
and accidental death cover are optional
benefits by ICICI brew
I protect smart we at ICICI Prudential
believe that every claim represents
fulfillment of a promise made to our
policyholders
we are committed towards securing the
future of your loved ones in a manner
that's quick and efficient in case the
policy holder or the nominee needs to
register a claim please write to claimed
care at ICICI brew live.com or log in to
the claims section of www ICICI prolong
our claim settlement ratio for financial
year 2014 and 2015 is ninety three point
eight zero percent we welcome you to the
ICICI Prudential Family and look forward
to serving you for a long time for any
further queries about your policy log on
to www.mptv.org/outdoorwisconsin
[Music]